(this.webpackJsonpwwbm=this.webpackJsonpwwbm||[]).push([[0],[,,,,,,function(e){e.exports=JSON.parse('{"levels":[{"reward":500,"difficulty":1},{"reward":1000,"difficulty":1},{"reward":2000,"difficulty":1},{"reward":4000,"difficulty":2},{"reward":8000,"difficulty":2},{"reward":16000,"difficulty":2},{"reward":32000,"difficulty":3},{"reward":64000,"difficulty":3},{"reward":125000,"difficulty":4},{"reward":250000,"difficulty":4},{"reward":500000,"difficulty":5},{"reward":1000000,"difficulty":5}],"questions":[{"id":18,"question":"Which of these signs does not appear in musical notation?","answers":[{"value":"Flat","key":3},{"value":"\\"For rent\\"","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Sharp","key":2},{"value":"Natural","key":4}],"difficulty":1},{"id":21,"question":"The word \\"grand\\" is slang for what amount of money?","answers":[{"value":"$100","key":3},{"value":"$1","key":2},{"value":"$1,000,000","key":4},{"value":"$1,000","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":1},{"id":4,"question":"Which of the following snack foods comes packaged with a \\"toy surprise\\"?","answers":[{"value":"Munchos","key":3},{"value":"U-bet chocolate syrup","key":4},{"value":"Cracker Jack","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Fiddle Faddle","key":2}],"difficulty":1},{"id":15,"question":"According to their longtime nickname, what kind of \\"duo\\" are Batman & Robin?","answers":[{"value":"Dangerous","key":3},{"value":"Dynamic","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Dynastic","key":2},{"value":"Delirious","key":4}],"difficulty":1},{"id":91,"question":"Something that is easily accomplished is said to be \\"like taking candy from a\\" what?","answers":[{"value":"Dentist","key":4},{"value":"Vending machine","key":2},{"value":"Baby","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Wrapper","key":3}],"difficulty":1},{"id":64,"question":"According to a popular saying, a finely attired person is said to be \\"dressed to\\" what?","answers":[{"value":"Steal","key":2},{"value":"Assault","key":3},{"value":"Embezzle","key":4},{"value":"Kill","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":1},{"id":73,"question":"If you make a serious effort to do something, you are said to \\"give it the old\\" what?","answers":[{"value":"Academy Award","key":2},{"value":"Navy purchase","key":3},{"value":"College try","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"School rap","key":4}],"difficulty":1},{"id":89,"question":"At which of these restaurants are you most likely to find T-bones and tenderloins on the menu?","answers":[{"value":"Steakhouse","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Vegetarian","key":3},{"value":"Seafood","key":2},{"value":"Ice cream parlor","key":4}],"difficulty":1},{"id":100,"question":"A person described as \\"Goth\\" typically wears what color clothes?","answers":[{"value":"Black","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Robin\'s egg blue","key":4},{"value":"Khaki","key":2},{"value":"Shocking pink","key":3}],"difficulty":1},{"id":151,"question":"According to a popular phrase, a person who achieves success through others is \\"riding their\\" what?","answers":[{"value":"Sidecar","key":2},{"value":"Coattails","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Golden goose","key":4},{"value":"Rickshaw","key":3}],"difficulty":1},{"id":148,"question":"On the TV show \\"Seinfeld,\\" what is Jerry\'s profession?","answers":[{"value":"Real estate broker","key":2},{"value":"Stand-up comedian","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Soup chef","key":3},{"value":"Magazine editor","key":4}],"difficulty":1},{"id":150,"question":"According to a popular phrase, something that is close by is just a \\"hop, skip and\\" what \\"away\\"?","answers":[{"value":"Spring","key":4},{"value":"Hiccup","key":3},{"value":"Toss","key":2},{"value":"Jump","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":1},{"id":147,"question":"Which of the following organizations is most likely to employ a \\"repo man\\"?","answers":[{"value":"Football team","key":3},{"value":"Collection agency","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Recycling plant","key":2},{"value":"Sanitation department","key":4}],"difficulty":1},{"id":125,"question":"In the 1823 poem \\"\'Twas the Night Before Christmas,\\" what is \\"hung by the chimney with care\\"?","answers":[{"value":"Flypaper","key":4},{"value":"Stockings","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Pictures","key":2},{"value":"Ornaments","key":3}],"difficulty":1},{"id":197,"question":"According to a popular song, how much does a \\"shave and a haircut\\" cost?","answers":[{"value":"Fifty cents","key":3},{"value":"Three dimes","key":4},{"value":"Two bits","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"One dollar","key":2}],"difficulty":2},{"id":190,"question":"In the motion picture rating \\"NC-17,\\" what do the letters \\"NC\\" stand for?","answers":[{"value":"No Cursing","key":4},{"value":"No Children","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Naked Content","key":2},{"value":"Non-Conditional","key":3}],"difficulty":2},{"id":227,"question":"Excluding the end zones, how long is a standard American football field?","answers":[{"value":"50 yards","key":2},{"value":"100 yards","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"200 yards","key":3},{"value":"500 yards","key":4}],"difficulty":2},{"id":199,"question":"Which of the following numbers reads the same when turned upside-down as it does right-side-up?","answers":[{"value":"9808","key":4},{"value":"1006","key":2},{"value":"1089","key":3},{"value":"8008","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":2},{"id":188,"question":"Which of these sleeve types traditionally requires the use of cuff links?","answers":[{"value":"Barrel cuffs","key":3},{"value":"French cuffs","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Knit cuffs","key":2},{"value":"Fringed cuffs","key":4}],"difficulty":2},{"id":311,"question":"A person who loves someone deeply is said to \\"carry a\\" what for them?","answers":[{"value":"Lantern","key":2},{"value":"Match","key":4},{"value":"Torch","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Flashlight","key":3}],"difficulty":2},{"id":311,"question":"A person who loves someone deeply is said to \\"carry a\\" what for them?","answers":[{"value":"Torch","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Match","key":4},{"value":"Flashlight","key":3},{"value":"Lantern","key":2}],"difficulty":2},{"id":248,"question":"In the title of the 1964 Roy Orbison song, what exclamation appears before the words \\"Pretty Woman\\"?","answers":[{"value":"Yikes","key":4},{"value":"Oh","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Wow","key":2},{"value":"Yeah","key":3}],"difficulty":2},{"id":255,"question":"What is the English translation of the German word \\"gesundheit\\"?","answers":[{"value":"Health","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Loud noise","key":4},{"value":"Feel better","key":3},{"value":"Nice sneeze","key":2}],"difficulty":2},{"id":290,"question":"In the lyrics of the song \\"As Time Goes By\\" from the 1942 movie \\"Casablanca,\\"  \\"a kiss is just\\" what?","answers":[{"value":"A kiss","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"For lovers","key":4},{"value":"A treat","key":3},{"value":"Romantic","key":2}],"difficulty":2},{"id":342,"question":"How many letters represent all the modern Roman numerals?","answers":[{"value":"6","key":3},{"value":"7","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"8","key":4},{"value":"5","key":2}],"difficulty":2},{"id":314,"question":"Which of these movies is not primarily set on a submarine?","answers":[{"value":"Das Boot","key":3},{"value":"Crimson Tide","key":2},{"value":"Apocalypse Now","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Down Periscope","key":4}],"difficulty":2},{"id":315,"question":"Who is Flash Gordon\'s archenemy?","answers":[{"value":"Doctor Octopus","key":2},{"value":"Ming the Merciless","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Lex Luthor","key":4},{"value":"Sinestro","key":3}],"difficulty":2},{"id":322,"question":"American historical figure John Brown is famous for fighting against what in the 1850s?","answers":[{"value":"Slavery","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Prohibition","key":2},{"value":"Colonization","key":3},{"value":"Taxation","key":4}],"difficulty":2},{"id":317,"question":"What motorcycle company produces the trademarked model called the \\"Fat Boy\\"?","answers":[{"value":"Harley-Davidson","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"BMW","key":4},{"value":"Triumph","key":2},{"value":"Yamaha","key":3}],"difficulty":2},{"id":346,"question":"What cartoon character\'s theme song warns him to \\"watch out for that tree\\"?","answers":[{"value":"Yogi Bear","key":2},{"value":"Bullwinkle","key":3},{"value":"Fred Flintstone","key":4},{"value":"George of the Jungle","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":3},{"id":370,"question":"The landmark Supreme Court case \\"Brown v. Board of Education\\" concerned what issue?","answers":[{"value":"Teaching of evolution","key":2},{"value":"School desegregation","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Affirmative action","key":4},{"value":"School prayer","key":3}],"difficulty":3},{"id":368,"question":"The 1992 movie \\"A League of Their Own\\" is set during what war?","answers":[{"value":"Vietnam War","key":4},{"value":"Korean War","key":3},{"value":"World War II","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"World War I","key":2}],"difficulty":3},{"id":366,"question":"In the 1993 movie \\"Addams Family Values,\\" what substance covers Cousin Itt?","answers":[{"value":"Bandages","key":2},{"value":"Scales","key":3},{"value":"Hair","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Cobwebs","key":4}],"difficulty":3},{"id":353,"question":"Which of the following is a popular brand of golf club made by Callaway?","answers":[{"value":"Big Bertha","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Killer Kathy","key":3},{"value":"Straight Sally","key":4},{"value":"Happy Hilda","key":2}],"difficulty":3},{"id":382,"question":"General Manuel Noriega was the de facto leader of what country?","answers":[{"value":"Honduras","key":3},{"value":"Haiti","key":2},{"value":"Colombia","key":4},{"value":"Panama","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":3},{"id":387,"question":"What is a \\"rapscallion\\"?","answers":[{"value":"Chopped onion","key":4},{"value":"Lounge singer","key":3},{"value":"Galloping horse","key":2},{"value":"Mischievous person","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":3},{"id":375,"question":"Which of these people is most likely to use a lathe as part of his or her profession?","answers":[{"value":"Pilot","key":3},{"value":"Carpenter","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Astrophysicist","key":4},{"value":"Barber","key":2}],"difficulty":3},{"id":375,"question":"Which of these people is most likely to use a lathe as part of his or her profession?","answers":[{"value":"Barber","key":2},{"value":"Carpenter","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Astrophysicist","key":4},{"value":"Pilot","key":3}],"difficulty":3},{"id":396,"question":"Who was known as \\"The Junk Bond King\\" in the 1980s?","answers":[{"value":"Michael Milken","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Rupert Murdoch","key":3},{"value":"Donald Trump","key":2},{"value":"Warren Buffett","key":4}],"difficulty":3},{"id":434,"question":"According to a New Orleans Mardi Gras tradition, \\"King Cakes\\" are baked with what small plastic figure inside?","answers":[{"value":"Crown","key":2},{"value":"Rose","key":4},{"value":"Pig","key":3},{"value":"Baby","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":3},{"id":410,"question":"Which of these characteristics is a hallmark of \\"Queen Anne\\" furniture?","answers":[{"value":"Mother of pearl inlay","key":3},{"value":"Curved legs","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Gold leaf surfaces","key":4},{"value":"Intricate ornamentation","key":2}],"difficulty":3},{"id":432,"question":"What state was the original home of the Los Angeles Lakers basketball team?","answers":[{"value":"Minnesota","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Florida","key":4},{"value":"Washington","key":3},{"value":"Wisconsin","key":2}],"difficulty":3},{"id":409,"question":"Former United Nations Secretary-General Dag Hammarskjold was from what Scandinavian nation?","answers":[{"value":"Denmark","key":3},{"value":"Sweden","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Finland","key":2},{"value":"Norway","key":4}],"difficulty":3},{"id":408,"question":"Who is the cowboy lead hero of the 1943 musical \\"Oklahoma!\\"?","answers":[{"value":"Will","key":3},{"value":"Curly","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Jud","key":2},{"value":"Jake","key":4}],"difficulty":3},{"id":464,"question":"Francis Gary Powers is famous for piloting what historic U.S. aircraft?","answers":[{"value":"First Stealth bomber","key":4},{"value":"Enola Gay bomber","key":2},{"value":"Apollo 13 spacecraft","key":3},{"value":"U-2 spy plane","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":4},{"id":468,"question":"In the 1981 movie \\"Stripes,\\" what is the birth name of the character known as \\"Psycho\\"?","answers":[{"value":"Hulka","key":4},{"value":"Russell","key":3},{"value":"Francis","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Dewey","key":2}],"difficulty":4},{"id":456,"question":"What former advisor to Bill Clinton wrote the 1999 political memoir \\"All Too Human\\"?","answers":[{"value":"George Stephanopoulos","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Dick Morris","key":4},{"value":"James Carville","key":2},{"value":"Dee Dee Myers","key":3}],"difficulty":4},{"id":457,"question":"In the original Spider-Man comics, what is the name of Peter Parker\'s supermodel girlfriend?","answers":[{"value":"Mary Ann","key":4},{"value":"Mary Jane","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Mary Jo","key":2},{"value":"Mary Beth","key":3}],"difficulty":4},{"id":497,"question":"By definition, what part of a flag is closest to the pole from which it flies?","answers":[{"value":"Shield","key":4},{"value":"Hoist","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Fly","key":3},{"value":"Charge","key":2}],"difficulty":4},{"id":490,"question":"Runaway slave Crispus Attucks was killed during what conflict of the American Revolution?","answers":[{"value":"Battle of Concord","key":3},{"value":"Boston Massacre","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Battle of Bunker Hill","key":2},{"value":"Battle of Saratoga","key":4}],"difficulty":4},{"id":506,"question":"How many colored circles are on a standard Twister mat?","answers":[{"value":"30","key":2},{"value":"24","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"32","key":3},{"value":"36","key":4}],"difficulty":4},{"id":501,"question":"In a 1999 vote, Americans chose what TV show to appear in a series of stamps commemorating the 1980s?","answers":[{"value":"The Cosby Show","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"L.A. Law","key":4},{"value":"Miami Vice","key":2},{"value":"Cheers","key":3}],"difficulty":4},{"id":489,"question":"Which of these movies is based on a Pulitzer Prize-winning novel by Oscar Hijuelos?","answers":[{"value":"Carlito\'s Way","key":4},{"value":"The House of the Spirits","key":3},{"value":"A Walk in the Clouds","key":2},{"value":"The Mambo Kings","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":4},{"id":523,"question":"Which of these pairs of gods are not equivalents in Greek and Roman mythology?","answers":[{"value":"Hermes and Mercury","key":2},{"value":"Apollo and Vulcan","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Hades and Pluto","key":3},{"value":"Zeus and Jupiter","key":4}],"difficulty":4},{"id":519,"question":"Three Mile Island, site of a 1979 nuclear accident, is located on what eastern U.S. river?","answers":[{"value":"Monongahela","key":4},{"value":"Susquehanna","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Delaware","key":2},{"value":"Allegheny","key":3}],"difficulty":4},{"id":529,"question":"In the 1957 Dr. Seuss story \\"How the Grinch Stole Christmas,\\" what mountain overlooks Who-ville?","answers":[{"value":"Mt. Crumpit","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Mt. Who","key":2},{"value":"Mt. Horton","key":3},{"value":"Mt. Snowy","key":4}],"difficulty":4},{"id":518,"question":"Martin Luther King, Jr. earned a doctorate degree from what university in 1955?","answers":[{"value":"Tuskegee Institute","key":3},{"value":"University of Alabama","key":4},{"value":"University of Chicago","key":2},{"value":"Boston University","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":4},{"id":522,"question":"Which of the following bodies of water lies directly off the north coast of the sultanate of Brunei?","answers":[{"value":"Coral Sea","key":4},{"value":"Yellow Sea","key":3},{"value":"South China Sea","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Arabian Sea","key":2}],"difficulty":4},{"id":557,"question":"Which of these cities is located in Russia?","answers":[{"value":"Odessa","key":4},{"value":"Minsk","key":3},{"value":"Omsk","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Kiev","key":2}],"difficulty":5},{"id":561,"question":"Which of these actors played a landlord in the original cast of the Broadway musical \\"Rent\\"?","answers":[{"value":"David Alan Grier","key":3},{"value":"Taye Diggs","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Omar Epps","key":2},{"value":"Don Cheadle","key":4}],"difficulty":5},{"id":541,"question":"What modern artist often painted graffiti using the pseudonym \\"SAMO\\" in locations around New York City?","answers":[{"value":"Jean-Michel Basquiat","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"David Hockney","key":2},{"value":"Andy Warhol","key":3},{"value":"Keith Haring","key":4}],"difficulty":5},{"id":542,"question":"In the 1957 movie \\"The Bridge on the River Kwai,\\" the bridge is near the border of what two countries?","answers":[{"value":"China & Laos","key":3},{"value":"Thailand & Cambodia","key":4},{"value":"China & Vietnam","key":2},{"value":"Thailand & Burma","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":5},{"id":546,"question":"In the century-long history of the Westminster Kennel Club dog show, what breed has won the most \\"Best in Show\\" titles?","answers":[{"value":"Poodle","key":4},{"value":"Spaniel","key":3},{"value":"Terrier","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Boxer","key":2}],"difficulty":5},{"id":583,"question":"The entertainer Cher is descended from what Native American tribe?","answers":[{"value":"Pueblo","key":3},{"value":"Cherokee","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Blackfoot","key":4},{"value":"Navajo","key":2}],"difficulty":5},{"id":563,"question":"According to Greek myth, which of these was not the name of one of Agamemnon\'s children?","answers":[{"value":"Electra","key":2},{"value":"Phaedra","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Iphigenia","key":4},{"value":"Orestes","key":3}],"difficulty":5},{"id":581,"question":"What author\'s 1900 novel \\"Sister Carrie\\" caused a scandal with its depiction of adultery?","answers":[{"value":"Theodore Dreiser","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Willa Cather","key":4},{"value":"Frank Norris","key":2},{"value":"Henry James","key":3}],"difficulty":5},{"id":573,"question":"At the age of 26, Edward Rutledge was the youngest person to do what?","answers":[{"value":"Climb Mt. Everest","key":3},{"value":"Sign Decl. of Independence","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Swim English Channel","key":2},{"value":"Win a Nobel prize","key":4}],"difficulty":5},{"id":620,"question":"In 1965, what was the first nation to withdraw from the United Nations?","answers":[{"value":"North Vietnam","key":3},{"value":"Indonesia","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"USSR","key":2},{"value":"Dominican Republic","key":4}],"difficulty":5},{"id":622,"question":"Who was the first U.S. president born in the 1800s?","answers":[{"value":"Abraham Lincoln","key":3},{"value":"Millard Fillmore","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Zachary Taylor","key":2},{"value":"John Tyler","key":4}],"difficulty":5},{"id":625,"question":"The English word \\"planet\\" is derived from a Greek word \\"planetes\\" meaning what?","answers":[{"value":"Pearl","key":4},{"value":"Night","key":3},{"value":"Wanderer","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Heaven","key":2}],"difficulty":5},{"id":615,"question":"For most of his 15 years in exile, Iran\'s Ayatollah Khomeini lived in what country?","answers":[{"value":"England","key":3},{"value":"Afghanistan","key":4},{"value":"France","key":2},{"value":"Iraq","key":1,"correct":true}],"difficulty":5},{"id":604,"question":"In his earliest \\"pop dot\\" paintings, the artist Roy Lichtenstein used what household item to paint the dots?","answers":[{"value":"Toothbrush","key":1,"correct":true},{"value":"Comb","key":3},{"value":"Kitchen sponge","key":2},{"value":"Medicine dropper","key":4}],"difficulty":5}]}')},,,,,,function(e,a,t){},function(e,a,t){},function(e,a,t){},,function(e,a,t){},function(e,a,t){},function(e,a,t){},function(e,a,t){},function(e,a,t){"use strict";t.r(a);var r=t(1),i=t.n(r),s=t(7),n=t.n(s),o=(t(12),t(3)),l=t(2),u=(t(13),t.p+"static/media/thumb-up.df3dc3a8.svg"),c=(t(14),t(0)),y=function(e){var a=e.children,t=e.className;return Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:["splash-view inline-content block-content",t||""].join(" "),children:[Object(c.jsx)("aside",{children:Object(c.jsx)("img",{className:"splash-view-image",src:u,alt:"",width:"312",height:"184"})}),Object(c.jsx)("main",{children:a})]})},d=t(4),h=(t(16),function(e){var a=e.children,t=e.className,r=e.href,i=e.tag,s=void 0===i?r?"a":"button":i,n=Object(d.a)(e,["children","className","href","tag"]);return Object(c.jsx)(s,Object(l.a)(Object(l.a)({className:["button",t].join(" "),href:r},n),{},{children:a}))});h.defaultProps={href:null};var v=h,f=(t(17),function(e){var a=e.children,t=e.className,r=e.status,i=Object(d.a)(e,["children","className","status"]);return Object(c.jsx)("li",Object(l.a)(Object(l.a)({className:["option",r||"",t].join(" ")},i),{},{children:Object(c.jsx)("button",{type:"button","aria-pressed":"selected"===r,children:a})}))}),k=function(e){var a=e.items,t=e.className,r=e.onSelect,i=Object(d.a)(e,["items","className","onSelect"]);return Object(c.jsx)("ol",Object(l.a)(Object(l.a)({className:["option-list",t||""].join(" ")},i),{},{children:a.map((function(e){var a=e.caption,t=e.value,i=e.selected,s=e.correct,n=[i&&!s&&"wrong",s&&"correct",i&&"selected"].find((function(e){return e}));return Object(c.jsx)(f,{status:n,onClick:function(){return r(t||a)},children:a||t},t)}))}))},w=(t(18),function(e){var a=e.children,t=e.status,r=e.className,i=Object(d.a)(e,["children","status","className"]);return Object(c.jsx)("li",Object(l.a)(Object(l.a)({className:["step",t,r||""].join(" ")},i),{},{children:a}))});w.defaultProps={status:"future"};var m=function(e){var a=e.items,t=e.className,r=Object(d.a)(e,["items","className"]);return Object(c.jsx)("ol",Object(l.a)(Object(l.a)({className:["step-list",t||""].join(" ")},r),{},{children:a.map((function(e){var a=e.caption,t=e.status,r=void 0===t?"future":t;return Object(c.jsx)(w,{status:r,children:a},a)}))}))},p=function(e){var a=e.onStart;return Object(c.jsxs)(y,{className:"welcome-view",children:[Object(c.jsx)("h1",{className:"headline",children:"Who wants to be a millionaire?"}),a&&Object(c.jsx)(v,{onClick:a,children:"Start"})]})};p.defaultProps={onStart:null};var b=p,g=new Intl.NumberFormat("en-US",{style:"currency",currency:"USD",minimumFractionDigits:2,maximumFractionDigits:2}),j=function(e){return g.format(e).slice(0,-3)},q=(t(19),function(e){var a=e.levels,t=e.reward,i=void 0===t?0:t,s=e.question,n=e.answers,l=e.onAnswer,u=function(){var e=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]&&arguments[0],a=Object(r.useState)(e),t=Object(o.a)(a,2),i=t[0],s=t[1],n=Object(r.useCallback)((function(){return s((function(e){return!e}))}),[s]);return[i,n]}(),y=Object(o.a)(u,2),d=y[0],h=y[1],v=n,f=a.map((function(e){var a=e.reward,t=e.current,r=e.passed;return{caption:j(a),status:[r&&"past",t&&"current","future"].find((function(e){return e}))}}));return Object(c.jsxs)("div",{className:"play-view",children:[Object(c.jsx)("h1",{className:"visually-hidden",children:"Who wants to be a millionaire?"}),Object(c.jsxs)("main",{className:"play-view-main block-content inline-content",children:[Object(c.jsxs)("h2",{className:"visually-hidden",children:["Question for",j(i)]}),Object(c.jsx)("p",{className:"question play-view-question",children:s}),Object(c.jsx)(k,{className:"play-view-option-list",items:v,onSelect:l})]}),Object(c.jsxs)("aside",{className:"play-view-sidebar block-content ".concat(d?"open":""),children:[Object(c.jsx)("h2",{className:"visually-hidden",children:"Game steps"}),Object(c.jsx)(m,{items:f})]}),Object(c.jsx)("button",{className:"play-view-sidebar-toggle",type:"button",onClick:h,"aria-pressed":d,children:"Open levels view"})]})}),O=function(e){var a=e.finalReward,t=e.onRetry;return Object(c.jsxs)(y,{className:"result-view",children:[Object(c.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(c.jsx)("h2",{className:"question muted",children:"Total score:"}),Object(c.jsxs)("p",{className:"headline",children:["$\u200a",a," ","earned"]})]}),t&&Object(c.jsx)(v,{onClick:t,children:"Try again"})]})};O.defaultProps={onRetry:null};var S=O,C=t(6),N=function(){var e=C.levels,a=C.questions.slice().sort((function(){return Math.floor(10*Math.random())-5})),t=new Set;return e.map((function(e){var r=a.find((function(a){return!t.has(a)&&a.difficulty===e.difficulty}));return t.add(r),Object(l.a)(Object(l.a)({},e),{},{question:r})}))},A=function(){var e=function(){var e=Object(r.useRef)(null);return null==e.current&&(e.current=N()),[e.current,N]}(),a=Object(o.a)(e,2),t=a[0],i=a[1],s=Object(r.useState)(0),n=Object(o.a)(s,2),l=n[0],u=n[1],c=Object(r.useState)(!1),y=Object(o.a)(c,2),d=y[0],h=y[1],v=t[l],f=v.question,k=null!=t[l-1]?t[l-1].reward:0;return{levels:t,currentLevel:v,currentReward:k,isOver:d,processAnswer:function(e){if(function(e){var a=f.answers.find((function(a){return a.value===e}));return a&&a.correct}(e)){var a=l+1;u(a),a>=t.length&&h(!0)}else h(!0)},restart:function(){i(),u(0),h()}}},W=function(){var e=A(),a=function(e){var a=e.answers,t=e.processAnswer,i=(arguments.length>1&&void 0!==arguments[1]?arguments[1]:{}).timeout,s=void 0===i?2e3:i,n=Object(r.useState)(""),l=Object(o.a)(n,2),u=l[0],c=l[1];return{answers:a.map((function(e){var a=e.value,t=e.correct;return{value:a,correct:""!==u&&t,selected:a===u}})),processAnswer:function(e){c(e),setTimeout((function(){t(e),c("")}),s)}}}({answers:e.currentLevel.question.answers,processAnswer:e.processAnswer}),t=a.answers,i=a.processAnswer,s=e.currentLevel.question,n=function(e,a){var t=!1;return e.map((function(e){var r={reward:e.reward,current:e===a,passed:!t&&e!==a};return e===a&&(t=!0),r}))}(e.levels,e.currentLevel),l=Object(r.useState)(!1),u=Object(o.a)(l,2),y=u[0],d=u[1];return y?e.isOver?Object(c.jsx)(S,{finalReward:e.currentReward,onRetry:e.restart}):Object(c.jsx)(q,{levels:n,question:s.question,answers:t,onAnswer:i}):Object(c.jsx)(b,{onStart:function(){return d(!0)}})};n.a.render(Object(c.jsx)(i.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(c.jsx)(W,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}],[[20,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.53927e43.chunk.js.map